[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When and where was Ron White born?", "correct_answer": "December 18, 1956 in Fritch, Texas", "incorrect_answers": ["November 20, 1960 in Oklahoma City, Oklahoma", "September 4, 1958 in Kansas City, Kansas", "October 18, 1955 in Amarillo, Texas"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "To what character from the 2004 movie Troy does this line belong: This war will never be forgotten. Nor will the heroes who fight in it?", "correct_answer": "Odysseus", "incorrect_answers": ["Achilles", "Helen", "Agamemnon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is a French dish, whose main ingredients are veal, onions and mushrooms?", "correct_answer": "Blanquette de veau", "incorrect_answers": ["Souffle", "Pot-au-feu", "Coq au Vin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does POS mean in instant messaging language?", "correct_answer": "parent over shoulder", "incorrect_answers": ["please open soon", "passing off as stupid", "pressing on solo (going it alone)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When Yugoslavia collapsed, one of its republics became an independent state known as FYROM. To which country does the acronym refer?", "correct_answer": "Macedonia", "incorrect_answers": ["Albania", "Bosnia and Herzegovina", "Montenegro"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What happened to the Allspark after the movie Transformers came out?", "correct_answer": "It was sold on eBay.", "incorrect_answers": ["It was kept for sequels.", "It was lost.", "It was given to a friend."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Academy Award did the 1997 movie L.A. Confidential win?", "correct_answer": "Best Actress in a Supporting Role", "incorrect_answers": ["Best Actor", "Best Director", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who proposed a general method of classifying how technologically advanced a civilization is?", "correct_answer": "Kardashev", "incorrect_answers": ["Fujita", "Tanner", "Malinas"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The term for the conclusive position in one of the worlds most popular board games - chess, comes from the Persian phrase Shah Mat, which means what?", "correct_answer": "The king is dead.", "incorrect_answers": ["The king is captured.", "The king is conquered.", "Surrender the king."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On February 12, 2004 Barbie and Ken did this.", "correct_answer": "Broke up", "incorrect_answers": ["Had their first child", "Got married", "Committed suicide"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Did some trilobites filter-feed as a means of obtaining food?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of the following is often referred to as The Godfather of Hip Hop?", "correct_answer": "Kool DJ Herc", "incorrect_answers": ["Grandmaster Funk", "Robinata Troop", "U-Roy"]}]